本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
我们该怎么办  查岳
What do we do, Chadley?
我以为他们已经死了
I thought they were dead.
比那还糟  崔西安达
Far worse, Trixandra.
他们快死了但还没完全死透
They're nearly almost dead but not quite!
天啊  和真正的僵尸较量过之后
Man, these movies are a lot less scary
再看这类电影真是越来越不恐怖了
when you've actually fought real zombies.
他们太慢了
They're slow.
快步走都能甩掉他们
Just power-walk away from them.
你愿意赌多少钱那个人先死
How much you want to bet that guy dies first?
啊  我的脸被啃了一大口
Aah! My face is being eaten a lot.
查岳撞辉偎气迷人了
Chadley ain't pretty no more.
稍等
One second.
呃  罗比又发来条短信
Ugh, another text from Robbie.
哦  对  罗比
Oh, yeah, Robbie.
这个  他是怎么个情况
How's, uh, how's all that going?
我已经放下他了
Ugh, I'm over him.
真希望他也能早点放下我
I just wish he was over me.
你看这短信
Just look at these texts.
眨眼的哭脸
Winky frown?
这表情到底什么意思啊
What does that even mean?
你怎么不去
And you're not...
不去  找找别的男生  或者说
not like, seeing any other guys or...
我当然有啊
Of course I am.
见见我的新男友  伙计
Meet my new boyfriend, dude.
对  对
Right, right.
所以说
So...
这个  你懂的  我好奇你是否想要
So, you know, I was wondering if maybe you wanted to,
我是说  你跟我有没有可能
I mean, if--if you and me would ever,
我想说的是  你会不会
I mean, if maybe you...
想要参加明天我和梅宝的探秘之旅
Hmm, wanted to join me and Mabel on this mystery hunt tomorrow.
那些阴谋的东西什么的
Conspiracy stuff and all that.
就这些
That's all.
当然了  伙计
Yeah, dude.
我喜欢跟朋友一起混
I love doing junk with friends.
哟  查岳  小心点
Yo, Chadley, watch out!
对  因为我们就是这样嘛
Yeah. 'Cause that's what we are.
我们一直都只是
It's all we'll ever be...
亲爱的温蒂
今天我一定要告诉你
我喜欢你
是不是很疯狂？
朋友
Friends.
伙计  你躺在我胸罩上了
Dude, you're lying on my bra.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： WaitinZ
翻译： Shortcut  Tracy  莫莉什么的  战忽局副局座
■
校订  后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第二季第二集
Gravity Falls  S02E02  Into the Bunker
嘿  当心点
Hey, easy with that.
那全是用塑料做的
It's genuine plastic.
顺便把这个停车场上的裂缝也重新填一下吧
And re-pave the cracks in the parking lot while you're at it.
我可不想让我的车掉到中国去
I don't want my car falling into China.
派恩斯先生  到底是由什么引起的损坏
Mr. Pines, what exactly caused all this damage?
我要写份报告
I need to write a report.
呃  一个超大啄木鸟
Uh, a big woodpecker.
钱拿好
Keep the change.
我在眼罩下对你使眼色
I'm winking under my eye patch.
对我很有效哦
Works for me.
话说那些熊孩子跑哪里去了
Now where'd those kids run off to?
感谢各位的到来
Thank you all for coming.
嘿  哪里有神秘
Hey, when there's a mystery,
哪里就有你姐  解密
you can count on your sister-ee.
好厉害的押韵
That's an amazing rhyme.
当你想要些好
"When you want some good--
当你需要苏斯时
When, when you need a Soos..."
你  神啊  就是押不了韵
You've-- Oh, gosh. I don't know.
我们来这儿是为了解决重力泉头号神秘事件
We're here to solve the number one mystery in Gravity Falls.
是谁写的这本日志
Who wrote this journal?
三十年前作者就销声匿迹
Thirty years ago the author vanished without a trace,
但根据新的线索
but according to this new clue,
我们也许会找到他秘密的藏身地点
we may have found his secret hiding place.
危险！
只要找到作者  我们就能解答所有的谜题
We find that author, we learn the answers to everything.
我们只需找到下去的路
We just need to figure out a way to get down there...
悠着点  同志们
Chop it down, dudes.
温蒂
Wendy.
噢  嘿  你来啦
Oh, hey. You came.
伙计  我已经迫不及待了
Dude, I'm so stoked about this.
我一直期盼着和你们一起探险呢
I've been wanting to go adventuring with you guys.
肯定比在家给老爸收拾烂摊子好玩
Sure beats picking up after my dad at home.
是谁把墙放那儿的
Who put that wall there?
感谢邀请  伙计
Thanks for the invite, man.
那当然了  无论何时你想要  我  我们总会  我们
Of course! Any time you want to-- I'm-- We're always-- Us.
哎哟喂
Uh-oh.
邀请温蒂加入我们的任务
Inviting Wendy on our mission?
姐猜这儿有奸情哟
Me thinks there's romance afoot.
才不是呢  听着梅宝
No, look Mabel.
我想通了  我已经放下温蒂了
I've thought this through, and I'm over Wendy.
我从各个角度都考虑过了
I've looked at it from every angle,
做那种事根本是无用功
and that thing was going nowhere.
我知道现在什么事对我最要紧
I know what matters to me now,
就是找到这本日志的作者
and it's finding the author of this journal.
哈  你能放得下温蒂
Ha! You're over Wendy?
（注：spectacles 眼镜，谐音“怀疑”）
请允许我对此深表怀疑
Allow me to put on my skepticals.
我已经向前看了  梅宝
I've moved on, Mabel.
你也该这样
You should, too.
深表怀疑
Skepticals.
嘿  只有我感觉是这样吗
Hey, is it just me
那个树枝看起来像个控制杆机关
or does that branch kind of look like a lever?
嗯  对
Huh. Yeah.
但我们该怎么上去呢
But how do we get up there?
看起来我们需要  一个梯子
Seems like we'd need, like, a ladder.
或者像是  高跷
Or, like, ladder shoes?
对  高跷
Yeah, ladder shoes.
我让苏斯画个草图
I'll get Soos to draw up a prototype.
噢  对了
Oh, yeah.
我小时候  我爸老逼我参加伐木竞赛
My dad used to make me compete in these lumberjack games when I was a kid.
我算是游刃有余了
Guess I kind of ruled at it.
什么情况
Whoa, whoa. What is that?
哦  不
Oh, no!
好的  同志们  目标出现
All right, guys. This is it.
切记  无论下面发生什么  我们都不能告诉其他人
Remember, whatever happens down there, we tell no one.
好  谁想打头
Now, who wants to go first?
神啊
Dude!
这也太酷了吧
This is so stupid cool.
貌似是个放射性尘埃躲避所
It's like a fallout shelter or something.
这一定是作者的
It must have belonged to the author.
我要把这个挂我我床头上
This is going over my bed.
我的脸上毛茸茸的
My face feels fuzzy.
不可思议
This is incredible.
貌似他在为灾难做准备
It's like he was preparing for a disaster.
但是什么样的灾难
But what kind of disaster
需要准备六十多年的物资呢
would need supplies for over sixty years?
我的神啊
Oh, my gosh.
狮门思分分乐
A Shmez dispenser.
我记得这些东西
I remember these things.
你说什么
What's that?
对  我当然要来点儿你的怀旧糖果
Yes, I will have some of your old-timey face food.
呃  都是灰尘
Ew. Dusty.
等等  伙计们
Wait, guys.
这个罐头好像是最近才打开的
I think this can was opened recently.
作者没准还活着  就在这儿
The author might still be alive, down here.
等一下
Wait a minute.
我想我知道他往哪边去了
I think I know where he might have gone.
哦  天啊
Oh, man.
这地方到底什么时候建的
Was this place built in the past or the future.
嗯  这房间怪诡异的
Yeah. This room is way creepy.
没迪普的网上历史记录诡异啦
Not as creepy as Dipper's Internet history.
什么情况  伙计们
What's going on, dudes?
当有毛毛虫在你脸上还真挺难害怕起来
It's hard to be scared with caterpillars on your face.
墙动了
Wall things.
墙现在正在疯狂乱动啊
Crazy wall things happening right now.
停不下来
Ugh. It won't stop.
迪普  我们该怎么办
Dipper, what do we do?
快啊  快啊
Come on, come on.
找到这四个符号  快
Find these four symbols. Quick.
每人踩一个
Everybody step on one.
第一个
One!
第二个
Two!
第三个
Three!
第四个
Four!
快跑过去
Run for it!
好  太好了
Yes! Yes!
真是
That was...
真是太疯狂了
That was nuts.
刚才多亏你才化险为夷
You ruled back there, man.
谢谢
Thanks.
仔细检查一下这间古怪的监视室
Get a load of this crazy surveillance room.
快看我  伙伴们
Check it out, dudes.
苏斯  苏斯
Soos. Soos.
你太逗了
That is hilarious.
嘿  老弟  你忘了你的马甲
Hey, Bro, you forgot your vest.
这是啥
What the--
亲爱的温蒂
"Dear Wendy.
我一直很喜欢
I've always had a crush on--"
我的天哪
Oh, my gosh.
嘿  迪普
Hey, Dipper!
快看我发现了什么
Look what I found.
你干啥  还给我
What are you-- Give me that.
我知道啦  我知道啦  我知道啦
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
原来你一直都没放下温蒂
You're not over Wendy at all.
你是打算今天向她表白吗
And you were going to tell her today?
不  我改主意了
No. I changed my mind.
这是个坏主意  只会让我自己丢脸
It's a bad idea, I'd just embarrass myself,
然后变成另外一个她讨厌的人  就像罗比
and then I'd be another guy she hates, like Robbie.
迪普  你应该告诉她
Dipper, you should just tell her already.
不管怎样  至少你不会再像现在这样纠结
One way or another, you'll feel better afterwards.
听我说  梅宝  不管我多想告诉她都开不了口
Look, Mabel, I can't tell her no matter how much I want to.
所以你就不要再提了  好吗
So just drop it, okay.
哥们儿
Dude.
迪普  快来看这个奇怪的铁柜子
Dipper, you got to check out this weird metal closet.
我是机器人  我有一个铁柜子
I am a robot. I have a metal closet.
来了
Coming.
这事就当没发生过
This never happened.
他想告诉她但是又不敢说
<i>He wants to tell her but he's scared.</i>
也许他需要一点动力
<i>Maybe he needs a little push.</i>
好主意  梅宝  谢了  梅宝
<i>Good idea, Mabel. Thanks, Mabel.</i>
弟弟  无论发生什么
Brother, whatever happens,
我只想让你知道
I just want you to know something.
我这是为你好
This is for your own good.
啥
What?
什么
What the--
梅宝  放我们出去
Mabel! Let us out!
我会放你出来的  迪普
Oh, I'll let you out, Dipper.
只要你告诉温蒂
As soon as you tell Wendy
你想跟她说的话
that thing you've been wanting to tell her!
以后你会感激我的
You'll thank me for this later.
她在说啥
What is she talking about?
没啥
Nothing.
梅宝又吃砂糖包了
Mabel's just been eating raw sugar packets again.
不要避重就轻
That's besides the point.
现在就放我出去
Let me out right now!
灯在哪儿
Ugh, where are the lights?
消毒完毕
一间隐藏的实验室
A hidden lab.
也许作者是在这里做实验的
Maybe the author did experiments down here.
那  你觉得又是谁挖了这些隧道
Uh, what do you think dug all these tunnels?
希望我们找不到答案
Let's hope we don't find out.
梅宝  快放我们出去
Mabel! Open up for real!
这里有个怪物
There's a monster in here!
哈  少骗我
Ha, nice try.
唯一的怪物是你的心魔  迪普
The only monsters are your own inner demons, Dipper.
至理真言
That is so wise.
迪普
Dipper.
快点说梅宝想让你说的话
Just say whatever Mabel wants you to say
然后她就会放我们出去了
so she'll let us out of here.
快说啊  迪普  就现在  老弟
Come on, Dipper. Now is the time, Bro!
温蒂  我  我
Wendy, I-- I...
我要另找出口
I'm gonna find another way out.
等等  你说什么
Wait, what?
老兄  我们这是去哪儿啊
Dude, where are we going?
-我们该怎么办  -我不知道
- What do we do? - I don't know.
滚开
Back!
滚开  你这恶心的畜生
Back, you heinous beast!
好了  我刚扯掉了怪物的舌头
Well, I just ripped out a monster's tongue.
是你
It's you.
快走吧
Hurry now.
我吓退它了  但是它还会再回来的
I scared it off, but it will regenerate.
我没料到会有访客
I wasn't expecting guests.
我已经在这下面待了很长时间了
I've been down here for a very long time.
几年  也可能是几周
Years. Weeks maybe.
我很怀念橘汁
I miss orange juice.
你还不明白
You don't understand.
你就是我要找的那个人
You're the guy I've been looking for!
他就是那个人
He's the guy?
温蒂  就是他
Wendy, it's the guy!
谁啊
The guy?
我有超多问题想问你
I've got, like, a jillion questions.
你为什么写那些日志
Why did you write the journals?
谁在跟踪你  你为什么建了这个地方
Who was after you? Why did you build this bunker?
孩子  我很想和你讨论这些
My boy, I'd love to discuss this in time.
但是我们现在有更紧迫的事情要做
But we have more pressing matters.
这是我的实验之一
It's one of my experiments.
变形怪
A shapeshifter.
可以变成它所见过任何人或物的样子
Able to take the form of anyone or anything it sees.
它从钢筋笼子里逃了出来
It broke free from a cage of solid steel.
独自抓这个怪物已经快把我折磨疯了
I've gone half-crazy trying to catch the creature alone.
不过现在你们来了
But now you're here.
你们能帮我吗
Will you help me catch it?
他们要在里面待一会儿了
Sure are taking their time in there.
嘿  我穿上白大褂拿公文包是不是看上去更智慧了
Hey, do I look smarter with this coat and briefcase?
我觉着自己更智慧了
I feel like I look smarter.
好炫酷啊
Razzle dazzle!
快看这个电视一样的玩意儿
Look at this tubey thing.
冷冻
Frozen.
解冻
Unfrozen.
冷冻
Frozen.
解冻
Unfrozen.
这上面写的啥
What's this biz?
试验 #210 “变形怪” 越来越危险了！
已低温冻结
试验编号210  变形怪
"Experiment number two-ten: The Shapeshifter."
变形怪
Shapeshifter?
伙计  迪普是不是
Uh, dude, didn't Dipper say
说有个怪物和他们在一起
there was a monster in there with them?
我还以为他是在开玩笑
I thought he was just joking.
你知道迪普的笑话从来都不好笑
You know, Dipper's jokes are terrible!
迪普
Dipper!
进来  进来
Come in. Come in.
我为这里的混乱道歉
I apologize for the state of things.
我从来没有过人类访客
I don't get many non-mole people visitors.
这个畜生一定有一些我们可以攻击的弱点
Now the beast must have some weakness that we can exploit.
我过去一直在研究它
I used to have my research on him,
但是可惜  多年前我丢了我的日志
but alas, I lost my journals so many years ago.
你是说日志吗
Did you say journals?
老兄  我发现了其中一本
Dude, I found one of them.
我就是靠它才找到这儿的
It's how I tracked you down here.
什么  怎么可能
What? Could it be?
孩子  我不知道该怎么感谢你
My boy, I can't express my gratitude.
太好了
Oh, yes.
这么多年终于找到了
After all these years.
温蒂
Wendy!
这里好黑
Oh, it's so dark.
我们怎么才能找到他们
How will we ever find them?
这个难题交给梅宝
Leave that to Mabel.
哇  炫酷
Whoa! Rad!
这种通电的衣服是不是存在着火隐患啊
Although, isn't electric clothing kind of like a fire hazard?
不
No.
是欢乐隐患才对
It's a fun hazard.
现在让我来照路
Now let me light the way!
我们来救你们了
We're coming for you dudes.
太好了
Yes, yes.
都在这里
It's all here.
温蒂  我们见到了真正的作者  是不是很不可思议
Wendy, isn't it amazing we're actually meeting the real author?
迪普  快看
Dipper. Look.
呃  那啥
Uh, you know what?
我们好像该走了
We should probably get going.
可以把日志还给我吗
Can I have my journal back?
你们哪儿都不许去
You're not going anywhere.
你喜欢我的真身吗
How do you like my true form?
快点承认吧  你喜欢我的真身
Go on, admit it, you like it.
是你
You!
你对真正的作者做了什么
What did you do to the real author?
你找不到他的
You'll likely never find him.
那个六指呆子失去原貌已经三十年了
That six-fingered nerd hasn't been himself in thirty years.
但是我很感谢你把这本日志带给我
But I do thank you for bringing me his journal.
我还在笼子里时  他经常写个不停
He used to write while I was in my cage.
好多种美妙的变形方式啊
So many wonderful forms to take.
我们得把日志拿回来
We've got to get that journal back.
嘿  身体掠夺者  给你这个
Hey, body-snatcher. Snatch this.
快跑  快跑  快跑
Run! Run! Run!
嘿  伙计们  迪普  温蒂
Oh, dudes. Dipper! Wendy!
梅宝  苏斯
Mabel! Soos!
等等  咱得小心
Wait. Careful.
我们怎么能断定他们就不是变形怪
How do we know they're not the shapeshifter?
说不定哦  梅宝  给我验验真假
Maybe I am. Mabel, inspect my shape.
我戳
Poke.
-再来一遍  -我戳
-Do that again.  - Poke.
比第一次更爽
Even better the second time.
这俩货绝对是本人
It's definitely them.
我的天啊  温蒂  你流血了
Oh, my gosh, Wendy, you're bleeding.
淡定  淡定
It's cool. It's cool.
不就是点血么  哥们儿
It's just blood, man.
别吓傻了
Don't freak out.
这是咋回事啊
What happened?
我们被变形怪攻击了
We got attacked by the shapeshifter.
他从笼子里跑出来  假装是日志的作者
He broke out of his cage, pretended to the author,
还试图抢走迪普的日志
and wants Dipper's journal.
那家伙要是进了小镇
Imagine if he escapes into town.
他就能变成任何东西
He could transform into anything.
那咱就再也不能相信任何人了
We could never trust anyone ever again.
那现在怎么办
What do we do?
这样吧
Well.
他把我们引到他的地盘  捉弄我们
He took us into his home, tricked us,
还打算送我们上西天
and tried to destroy us.
我看  咱们就以牙还牙好了
I say we return the favor.
迪普  孩子
Dipper, my boy.
快出来呀
Come out.
我得跟你说点事
I must speak with you!
快现身吧  你这个不能变形的懦夫
Reveal yourself, you single-formed human weakling.
天啊  迪普老弟
Oh, boy, Dipper.
这本书里的怪兽看起来都好厉害呢
That book sure is full of some great monsters.
你终于出现了
There you are.
噢  又来了个新的
Ooh! And a new one.
我是应该变成你呢
Should I be one?
还是你呢
Or the other.
一起变怎么样
How about both?
同志们  他来了  他来了
Guys, he's coming! He's coming!
就是现在  快  快  快
Now! Now! Now! Now! Now!
这玩意儿不顶用啊
It's not working, dude.
嘿  放开
Hey. Let go.
你给我放开他
You leave him alone.
温蒂
Wendy!
Wendy?
不要啊  不要啊  不
No, no, no, no, no!
你能听见我说话吗  天哪
Can you hear me? Oh.
千万别出事啊  快给我醒过来啊
Please be okay. Please be okay!
哦  不  不  这都怪我
Oh, no, oh, no! This is all my fault!
如果在储藏室的时候我就告诉你这些
If I had told you when we were in the closet
咱就不会惹上这么多麻烦了
we wouldn't be in this mess.
但我太害怕了  现在你可能受了重伤  甚至更糟
But I was too scared and now you could be hurt or worse
我这辈子再也没有机会告诉你
and I never even got a chance to tell you
我  好像  爱上你了  温蒂
I'm, like, in love with you Wendy.
迪普
Dipper?
你是温蒂
Wendy?
等等
Wait.
那她又是  小心
Then who is-- Look out!
快把日志给我
Give me back that journal!
休想
Never!
从我身上滚开
Get off me.
快给我
Give it back.
这是迪普的
It belongs to Dipper.
用斧头砍她  迪普
Hit her with the axe!
别听她的  迪普
Don't listen to her, Dipper!
她才是变形怪
She's the shapeshifter!
我搞不清楚谁是正版的啊
I don't know who's who!
给点提示
Give me a sign!
把他推进去
Push him in!
怎么回事
Huh?
冻住啦
Frozen!
不要啊  快放我出去
No. No! Let me out!
快离开这鬼地方吧  各位
Let's get out of here, dudes.
你以为你很聪明  是吧  迪普
You think you're so clever, don't you, Dipper?
你根本不知道你在跟谁做对
But you have no idea what you're up against.
你永远找不到那个作者
You'll never find the author.
而且  你再继续调查下去的话
If you keep digging,
你的下场会比你所能想象的还要凄惨
You'll meet a fate worse than you can imagine.
而这  就会是你死前的模样
And this will be the last form you ever take!
祝你做个好梦啊
Good luck sleeping tonight.
各位  今天我好像有点冒险过度了
Dude, I think I'm kind of adventured out for a little while.
一整天都是这个表情  我的脸都疼了
My face hurts from doing this all day.
嗯  但是你得承认  咱们都挺英雄的
Yeah, but you got to admit we're all total heroes.
嘿  谁想去吃点英雄早餐啊
Hey, who wants to go get some heroes breakfast, huh?
吃糖浆麦片喽
Syrup on cereal!
梅宝  你真有远见卓识
Mabel, you're a visionary.
嗯  温蒂  关于刚才的事
Look, Wendy, about earlier,
可能有点过于激动了
In the heat of the moment
可能说了一些蠢话
I might have said some dumb things and--
咱能假装这事没发生过吗
Can't we just pretend none of that ever happened?
求你了
Please.
哥们儿  哥们儿  真的没关系
Dude. Dude. It's okay.
其实我一直都知道一点
I always kind of knew.
啥  真的吗
Wait. You did?
是啊
Yeah, man.
我是说  你以为你一直在小声
I mean, you think I can't hear that stuff
嘀咕的那些话  我都听不见吗
you're constantly whispering under your breath?
天哪
Oh, man.
听我说  迪普
Listen, Dipper.
我感觉  真的  受宠若惊
I'm, like, super flattered.
但是我对你来说年龄太大了
But, I'm too old for you.
你明白我意思吧  对吗
I mean, you know that, right?
梅宝说  说出真相会让我感觉好些
Mabel said confessing would make me feel better.
那你现在感觉如何
Well, how do you feel?
焦虑  害怕  感觉浑身痒痒
Anxious. Scared. Kind of itchy.
哥们儿
Dude.
别痒痒啊
Don't be itchy, man.
跟你说实话吧
Let me tell you something.
在你出现之前  这个夏天简直无聊死了
This summer was super boring until you showed up.
你给我带来的快乐  比任何人都要多
I have more fun with you than, like, practically anybody else.
如果你不能继续做我的朋友  我可能会
And if you ever stop being my friend, I would, like,
恨不得把自己扔到无底洞里去
throw myself into the bottomless pit.
那咱们的关系现在不会太尴尬吧
So, things won't be too awkward now?
我刚刚跟我自己摔了一跤哎  哥们儿
I just wrestled myself, dude.
那才叫尴尬呢
That was awkward.
如果你能解决那只怪物
If you can handle that monster,
那么解决一点小小的尴尬  当然不在话下
you can handle a little awkwardness.
还是朋友吧
Friends?
嗯哪  绝对的朋友
Yeah, dude. Friends.
哦  还有件事  迪普
Oh, and hey, Dipper.
明天电影之夜再见
See you for movie night tomorrow.
这次在你家吧  好么
Your place this time, okay?
进展顺利吗
So, how did it go?
你听到啥了
What did you hear?
我都听到了  我一直在这里
Everything. All the time.
我可不在这里
I'm not here.
梅宝  那一刻的感受怎么会
Mabel, how can everything be so amazing
那么美好又那么可怕呢
and so terrible all at the same time?
我也不应该这么心急的  迪普
I'm sorry for being so pushy, Dipper.
如果能安慰你的话
If it's any consolation,
我已经开始给你所有的
I'm already working on a list
潜在约会对象列表了
of your potential rebound crushes.
谢谢你了  梅宝
Thanks, Mabel.
没找着作者
I'm still bummed
我还是挺失望的
we're no closer to finding the author guy.
不过至少我弄到了他的白大褂和公文包
At least I got his sciency coat and briefcase.
哇  我嘞个
Whoa. What the--
苏斯  那可不是什么公文包  那是台笔记本电脑
Soos, that's not a briefcase. That's a laptop.
而且貌似它坏得还挺厉害的
And a really busted up one, too.
我敢说  几天内我就能把这玩意儿修好
I bet I could get this thing fixed up in a few days.
估计要花掉我不少胶带
It's gonna take a lot of duct tape.
这说不定会是咱的下一个线索
This could be our next clue.
归 F 所有
不光我这么想吧
Is it just me,
重力泉电视台就只会播这些烂片么
or does Gravity Falls TV only have the worst movies?
您正在收看的是  重力泉廉价电影大放送
You're watching the Gravity Falls Bargain Movie Showcase.
下面为您奉献
Coming up next,
《小小吸血鬼》
The Widdlest Wampire.
《星球“星球”上的星球人》
The Planet People Of Planet Planet!
《救命  我的木乃伊是狼人》
Help! My Mummy's A Werewolf!
《感叹号的进攻！！！》
Attack Of The Exclamation Points!!!
《味如嚼蜡男》
The Man With No Taste.
《鬼・龟》
Ghost Turtle.
《救命  我的木乃伊是狼人2：又变狼人了》
Help! My Mummy's A Werewolf Two: This Again.
打死你都不看这破频道了吧
You want to never watch this channel again?